A refund to you, I have heard here that
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Companies are very
favorite, you see, as per the research, they do
not want to take much risk
with their investment and if
they are getting returns more than debt, then they are satisfied with that, you
can consider it as adequate return,
suppose if you get returns of even 12 to 15 percent in a year
and it is quite safe, then
you should not neglect insurance companies, if you see the market right now, it is
ignoring a little bit,
it is completely good which has
come here as per the advertisement, but again the
kind of structure that is made, then
again the human, which will be seen being resumed to a friend, will have
soft all the characters,
but before all this comes to a heap, we will
buy 9 to 12 bands, and then we will make a purchase of this, then
approximately 20 to 25 percent of the
return can be seen very easily,
so fantastic, the serum from my side